<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en"><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.4.1">Jekyll</generator><link href="https://rdheerajp.github.io/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml"/><link href="https://rdheerajp.github.io/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" hreflang="en"/><updated>2025-09-06T14:58:47+00:00</updated><id>https://rdheerajp.github.io/feed.xml</id><title type="html">blank</title><subtitle>welcome to my corner of the interwebs. </subtitle><entry><title type="html">questions?</title><link href="https://rdheerajp.github.io/blog/2025/questions/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="questions?"/><published>2025-09-05T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2025-09-05T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://rdheerajp.github.io/blog/2025/questions</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://rdheerajp.github.io/blog/2025/questions/"><![CDATA[<p><em>Note: this post aims not to be easily understood, rather to be correctly understood.</em></p> <p>Welcome to ‘tilted’ - an assortment of random thoughts.</p> <p>I will go over my several attempts of writing this very post before settling on answering my own questions.</p> <h2 id="timeline">Timeline</h2> <p>I take a brisk walk through the years to set the context.</p> <ul> <li>2020: The world pauses. Attempt 1 at a personal page.</li> <li>2021: Hectic year. Graduation. Work. Leaving for a Masters.</li> <li>2022: More work. Attempt 2 at a personal page.</li> <li>2023:</li> <li>2024: Finally, started working on this page.</li> <li>2025: I guess this counts as a successful attempt.</li> </ul> <h2 id="qna">QnA</h2> <p>To put this out, I had to argue with the voices in my head. I answer them for myself, but also for others who partake in this madness.</p> <h4 id="q-tilted-why">Q. tilted? why?</h4> <p>The blog is titled ‘tilted’. Truth be told, it started with a typo. Now, I have a couple of justifications for this happy accident.</p> <p>First, the intention of this space is to share my perspective. The objective is to give room for subjectivity and bias, while maintaining openness and transparency. So, ‘tilted’ refers to my colored view of the world. It serves as a neat little heads up and cautions the reader to be aware of the inclinations.<sup id="fnref:1"><a href="#fn:1" class="footnote" rel="footnote" role="doc-noteref">1</a></sup></p> <p>Second, I play and watch a lot of chess. There, the term ‘being on a tilt’ refers to the frustation from a streak of losing. Nothing could capture the timeline of constant failure better. However, now that I have acknowledged the failures, I hope that the learnings will help me out. Fingers crossed.</p> <h4 id="q-expectations">Q. expectations?</h4> <p>… are the thief of joy. Nonetheless, here’s a non-exhaustive list of things I might do:</p> <ol> <li>Write. I want to get back into writing for leisure. Essays, poems and opinions. Anything I scratches my itch will eventually find its place among the bottomless pit that is the internet.</li> <li>Laze around. I know that I stay idle. I plan on continuining to do so. There is no regular programming or we’ll be right back.</li> </ol> <h4 id="q-worth-it">Q. worth it?</h4> <p>Figuring out the nitty-gritty of Docker containers, jekyll, Markdown, JS, and GitHub actions was fun.</p> <h4 id="q-2023">Q. 2023?</h4> <p>Glad you asked. I ran out of excuses and had to watch the keyboard collect dust.</p> <h2 id="footnotes">Footnotes</h2> <div class="footnotes" role="doc-endnotes"> <ol> <li id="fn:1"> <p>tilted ↔ inclined; inclinations ↔ proclivity, disposition. <a href="#fnref:1" class="reversefootnote" role="doc-backlink">&#8617;</a></p> </li> </ol> </div>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="overthinking"/><summary type="html"><![CDATA[answering the voices in my head.]]></summary></entry></feed>